





## WHO AM I?

Hi, my name is Adrian Karlén and I am a 29-year-old software developer based in Stockholm. My main focus is web development and I have previous work experience with technologies such as React, PHP, JS/TS and .NET. My everyday work have consisted of developing web-based business systems, e-commerce systems and customer portals. This have also included integration with external systems.



## **EXPERIENCE**

2022 - on going

Full stack developer @ SPP

At SPP my team is responsible for the web catering to the private customers. Here I have worked on two major projects:

- **Endowment client** Face lift of the old endowment client provided by SPP, inlcuded migrating from React 16 to 18, TypeScript-updates and design overhauls. During this I worked closely with UX-designers and business analysts.
- Fund change client Migration from an old Angular 1 web app to a React 18 app, rebuilding everything from scratch.

TypeScript / React / .NET

2022 - on going

Software consultant @ Viati

Main employment, did work at SPP via Viati.

2019 - 2022

Software consultant @ Exsitec

Post graduation work place, I worked as a software consultant focusing on CRM and later e-commerce. Some of my work here includes:

- · Casall Worked with their e-commerce solution and web shop.
- PTS Part of a team working with delivering a new system for applying for monetary support for broadband expansions. This included a portal for applicants and a back office solution with tons of automation to calculate support levels.

React / .NET / Litium / PHP / Symphony / underscore.js / Handlebars

2018 part time Summer internship @ Siemens Industrial Turbines

Python / .NET

2016 - 2018

Event technician/DJ @ ADK Event

Small business focusing on live audio mixing and DJing.

## **EDUCATION**

2016 - 2019

Bachelor's programme in Information Systems Analysis @ Linköping University

With a focus on software development Python / Java / C++ / Ada

LANGUAGES

**HOBBIES** 

NON PROFIT

**Swedish** - native **English** - proficient

I like playing board games and during summer I test my anger in golf. I also try to DJ whenever I get the chance.

Board member and in charge of bookings and sales in student association Forte @liu